<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MicroBlog</title>
    <link>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MicroBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is as good as Dianabol - Power or bulk?</title>
      <link>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/db-roid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/db-roid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;D bol benefit isn&amp;rsquo;t so much dependent from amount of pills , this helps every newbie to stick on a low dosage, receive the gain with no stress on body. Just 30 milligrams of Dianabol everyday quickly elevates anabolic foundation, so athlete is charged from first days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to save yourself from all the possibli side effects of juice steroid</title>
      <link>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/inj-roids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/inj-roids/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just couple of simple tips going to defend your overall health and provide purely positives out of injectables. For the oral bolins injects are most popular combination, blend blow up and you&amp;rsquo;re raking bulks. With no strong AS injections, current athletics doping is impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memories about unique properties of Durabolin types</title>
      <link>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/nan-roids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/nan-roids/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Oftentimes people assume ND betters NPP and viceversa, in real life, there&amp;rsquo;s absolutely no contrast. The specific type active-life provides the option of choosing specs - Nandrolone Phenylpropionate serves for the obvious hardness, Nandrolone Decanoate restores and heals faster. Type can&amp;rsquo;t vary main qualities of the item, as inside ampule there&amp;rsquo;s Durabolin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Influences of recovery pills</title>
      <link>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/recovery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the absence of Test hormone, Post cycle therapy meds can strengthen the emotional atmosphere. Sexual desire returns quickly. Testosterone is fine,6-pack - everything will be amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The facts about T hormone shots</title>
      <link>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/test/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apart from rate of taking to blood vessels, there are no deviation amongst test ethers. Synthetic Test can scare any beginner, because it is presented in various esters and Aquatest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sus 250 - quick review. Why it is so common in bodybuilding</title>
      <link>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/sus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/sus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Scientists revealed most significant testosteronic properties , then stuffed to one steroid. Leave the searches 4 easiest form - use Sustanon. Omnadren is very advantageous testosterone blend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roids with no risk - extra support during cycle</title>
      <link>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/roids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/roids/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Encourages precisely rational muscle builders, pushes main problems aside. Cycle Medicine provides effective administration of any combination. During cycle stuff boost anabolic payouts to their maximum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to arrange steroid cycle</title>
      <link>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/firstofall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electro-funk.github.io/jimmy/firstofall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If ever you want to make the progress with overall health perks - determine your personal ambitions correctly. Steroid assumes that the user understand the material, that is a thing to all progressed bodybuilders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>